Fear Not | Words Of Wisdom With TB Joshua
THOSE THAT ARE WITH US
ARE MORE THAN THOSE AGAINST US
FEAR NOT
FEAR CHANGES OUR FOCUS
FEAR WEAKENS OUR DETERMINATION AND WILL POWER.
FEAR IS A MORE DECEPTIVE ENEMY THAN SATAN HIMSELF.
FEAR NOT – THOSE WHO ARE WITH US, FIGHTING FOR US, PROTECTING US,
ARE MORE THAN THOSE WHO ARE AGAINST US TO DESTROY US.
THE ANGELS UNSPEAKABLY MORE NUMEROUS;
GOD INFINITELY MORE POWERFUL.
WHEN WE CANNOT SEE BEYOND OUR IMMEDIATE SITUATION, WE BEGIN TO PANIC.
WHEN WE ARE MAGNIFYING THE CAUSES OF OUR FEARS,
WE OUGHT TO POSSESS OURSELVES WITH CLEAR, GREAT AND HIGH
THOUGHTS OF GOD AND INVISIBLE WORLD.
IF GOD BE FOR US, WE KNOW WHAT FOLLOWS.
EVERY MOUNTAIN FOR OUR SAKE SHALL BE LEVELLED.
[AMEN!]
THE HILL WILL BECOME PLAIN.
WHEN WE WALK THROUGH FIRE, WE WILL NOT BE BURNT.
[AMEN!]
IF GOD BE FOR ME, EVERY MOUNTAIN SHALL BE LEVELLED.
THE HILL WILL BECOME PLAIN.
IF I PASS THROUGH FIRE, I WILL NOT BE BURNT.
DON'T BECAUSE OF YOUR TROUBLE CHANGE YOUR DIRECTION,
GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING.
DON'T BECAUSE OF YOUR TROUBLE CHANGE YOUR CONFESSION.
IN EVERY SITUATION GOD HAS SOMETHING TO SAY.
TELL YOUR NEIGHBOUR, "GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING".
[GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING.]
I WILL NOT BECAUSE OF MY SITUATION
CHANGE MY DIRECTION,
CHANGE MY CONFESSION.
GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING.
I WILL NOT BECAUSE OF YOU CHANGE MY POSITION, CHANGE MY DIRECTION.
GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING THROUGH YOU.
IT MAY BE TO STOP ME AWHILE.
WHAT CAN GOD SAY THROUGH YOUR SITUATION?
IT MAY BE TO STOP YOU AWHILE IN ORDER TO PRESERVE YOU.
IT MAY BE TO STOP YOU AWHILE IN ORDER TO CHECK YOU BECAUSE YOU ARE GOING TOO FAR.
IT MAY BE TO STOP YOU AWHILE IN ORDER TO PREPARE YOU FOR THE CHALLENGES AHEAD.
IT MAY BE TO STOP YOU AWHILE IN ORDER TO KEEP YOU FOR A NEW LEVEL.
IT MAY BE TO STOP YOU AWHILE IN ORDER TO REFORM YOU.
Fear Not | Words Of Wisdom With TB Joshua
TELL YOUR NEIGHBOUR, "I'M WALKING WITH THE LORD.
I'M NOT USED TO FAILURE,
I'M NOT USED TO DOUBT.
I'M WALKING WITH THE LORD.
Fear Not | Words Of Wisdom With TB Joshua
THEREFORE, I'M NOT WALKING BY SIGHT.
I'M WALKING WITH THE LORD.
WHAT IS SEEN CANNOT DICTATE MY DIRECTION.
WHAT IS SEEN CANNOT CHANGE MY CONFESSION.
I'M WALKING WITH THE LORD.
Fear Not | Words Of Wisdom With TB Joshua
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe, to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, sermons and testimonies
from the Synagogue Church of all Nations.
Emmanuel TV – changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 03/04/2019